https://www.englishpage.com/policy.htm

Englishpage Privacy Policy
We at Englishpage.com understand that privacy is important to our visitors. This privacy policy details the kind of information we receive as well as the steps we take to safeguard that information.
For each visitor, our server automatically recognizes the IP address, operating system, and browser. We DO NOT automatically detect or collect names, email addresses, or any other personal information. When you email Englishpage.com with a question or comment, your email address is NOT sold or shared with anyone outside of Englishpage.com.
We do use some third-party services which may place cookies or collect data. Each third-party service provider’s use of your personal information is dictated by their respective privacy policies. These third-party services include:
Google Adsense
Google and its network partners use cookies to serve personalized ads based on the websites you have visited. These personalized ads may appear on our site if you have not opted out of this service. You can adjust the settings or opt out of this personalized advertising by visiting Google Ad Settings. We also encourage our visitors to read through
Google's Privacy Policy to better understand how Google collects and uses your data.
Google Analytics
Each page on Englishpage.com uses Google Analytics code to measure visitor numbers. This service tracks website usage and provides information such as referring websites, pages you visit on Englishpage.com, operating system and browser. Google Analytics may log your IP address, but no other personal information is captured by Google Analytics (the data is anonymous). Again, we suggest our visitors visit Google's Privacy Policy to learn more about how they collect and use your data.
Social Media
Each page on Englishpage.com contains links to social media sites, so visitors can easily share our content. When you click through to these sites, they may collect data about you. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of Facebook, Twitter, Google, and Pinterest to learn more about the data they collect and
how you can view or delete that data.
Copyright ©
Englishpage.com, All Rights Reserved.
Contact us | Privacy Policy | Advertise with us
Your personal online English school. Learn English at Englishpage.com!
Weekly Lesson Grammar Book Vocabulary Verb Tenses Conditionals Modals Gerunds / Infinitives Articles Prepositions Mini-tutorials Irregular Verbs Reading Room
Listening Lounge Games English Schools Phrasal Verb Dictionary Verb + Preposition Dictionary
